umall.pk 2016-05-13

# Umall Privacy Policy

Ensuring you that [Umall.pk](http://umall.pk/ "Online Shopping Pakistan, Karachi, Lahore, Islamabad") has always committed to ensuring your privacy is protected, please read our privacy policy explaining the information which is collected from you and how in turn the information is used. By purchasing from [Umall](http://umall.pk/ "Online Shopping Pakistan, Karachi, Lahore, Islamabad").pk and all its sub-domains, you lie under our privacy policy. Our Privacy policy is completely concise and in linked with the current privacy laws. Umall.pk understands your privacy needs and will not sell, trade, or share personal information collected online from customers with third parties. All personal information collected by Umall.pk will only be used internally and exclusively within our corporate group. When you place order at Umall.pk your personal information will also be automatically used for marketing, updates and/or promotional purposes where you will be receiving email from us but you can choose to unsubscribe to our newsletters or promotional emails whenever you desire.

## DISCLOSURE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION

We collect information related to such transactions including the types and specifications of the goods, pricing and delivery information, any trade dispute records Umall.pk assurances that your personal information will not be shared with other organizations, except with the third-party providers used by us will only collect, use and disclose your information to the extent necessary to allow them to perform the services they provide to us.

## SECURITY OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

Your data is stored through in our data storage/databases. We store your data on a secure server behind a firewall. We treat data as an asset that must be protected and use lots of tools (encryption, passwords, physical security, etc.) to protect your personal information against unauthorized access and disclosure. However, as you probably know, third parties like Hackers and other illegal operational companies may unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private communications, other users may abuse or misuse your personal information that they collect from the site. Therefore, we work very hard to protect your privacy, we do not promise that your personal information or private communications will always remain private.

## CHANGES TO THE PRIVACY POLICY

Please do frequently check back as Umall.pk privacy policy may incorporate changes from time to time. Umall.pk reserves the right though to change and modify its privacy policy at any time. All changes to the privacy policy will be published on Umall.pk.

## ACCOUNT PROTECTION

To protect your personal information, we take reasonable precautions and follow industry best practices to make sure it is not inappropriately lost, misused, accessed, disclosed, altered or destroyed. Use strong passwords are they are the key to your account. Use unique numbers, letters and special characters, and do not disclose your Umall.pk password to anyone. Kindly remember that you are responsible for all actions taken in the name of your account. If you lose control of your password, you may lose significant control over your personal information and may be subject to legally binding actions taken on your behalf. Therefore, if your password has been compromised for any reason, please inform Umall.pk and change it as soon as possible.
